let's take a look at the process for
让我们来看看
debugging web application on an
调试Web应用程序
application server using IntelliJ IDEA
使用IntelliJ IDEA的应用程序服务器
so IntelliJ IDEA supports many many
因此IntelliJ IDEA支持许多
application servers Tomcat Tommy Yi
应用程序服务器Tomcat Tommy Yi
GlassFish and many more here I setup a
GlassFish等在这里我设置了一个
debug configuration for the Tomcat
调试Tomcat的配置
application server as long as you
应用服务器只要你
installed the application server on your
在您的计算机上安装了应用程序服务器
local machine and enabled the
本地计算机并启用了
application server integration plug-in
应用程序服务器集成插件
then IntelliJ IDEA should do a large
那么IntelliJ IDEA应该做大
part of this for you
这是你的一部分
a few important things to note typically
通常需要注意的一些重要事项
when you're developing a web application
在开发Web应用程序时
you'll be switching back and forth
你会来回切换
between the code and the finished result
在代码和最终结果之间
and so in order to do that quickly and
为了快速做到这一点，
efficiently you can simply update your
高效地，您只需更新您的
classes and resources without having to
类和资源，而不必
redeploy your entire application or
重新部署您的整个应用程序或
restart the server if you've enabled
重新启动服务器（如果已启用）
hot-swap in your settings and you're
热设置中的交换
working off of an exploded war like I've
像我一样，正在爆发战争
done here this format is less condensed
在此完成此格式的压缩较少
enabling you to swap in different
使您可以交换不同的
components inside your application
应用程序内部的组件
making it easy to write and deploy your
使其易于编写和部署
code on the fly one more thing you want
快速编写您想要的另一件事
to verify to get the full hot-swap
进行验证以获取完整的热交换
experience is to use update classes and
经验是使用更新类和
resources on frame deactivation what
关于帧停用的资源
this does is whenever you edit your
只要您编辑自己的
classes and resources in IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中的类和资源
then switch over to your browser and
然后切换到您的浏览器并
reload the page this will pull in those
重新加载页面，这将拉那些
new changes so whenever the frame for
新的变化，所以每当框架
your web application is deactivated this
您的Web应用程序已停用
happens automatically when I deploy my
部署我的设备时会自动发生
application I'll want to launch the
我要启动的应用程序
browser and attach a JavaScript debugger
浏览器并附加JavaScript调试器
if it's applicable for my application
如果适用于我的应用
now under the start of a connection tab
现在在连接选项卡的开始下
you can configure how IntelliJ IDEA
您可以配置IntelliJ IDEA
communicates with the application server
与应用服务器通信
you can see by default here there's some
您可以默认看到这里有一些
parameters here that tell JD WP which
告诉JD WP的参数
transport protocol to use the address
传输协议使用地址
and other flags that it should honor
和它应该遵守的其他标志
during the debug process here you can
在调试过程中，您可以
configure the port which the debugger
配置调试器要使用的端口
should connect through and provide any
应该通过连接并提供任何
pre launch directives to IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA的启动前指令
so now let's apply this and go ahead and
所以现在让我们应用这个并继续
debug our application IntelliJ IDEA is
调试我们的应用程序IntelliJ IDEA是
compiling the artifact and deploying it
编译工件并进行部署
to the application server right now
现在到应用程序服务器
it opens up our browser to the main page
它打开我们的浏览器到主页
inside our application and the first
在我们的应用程序和第一个
thing you'll notice is that as you'll
你会注意到的是
remember I've enabled the JavaScript
记得我已经启用了JavaScript
debugger inside my Tomcat run
Tomcat运行中的调试器
configuration and inside this file I've
配置，并在此文件中
set a JavaScript breakpoint on the first
在第一个上设置JavaScript断点
line of this function we can step
此功能行我们可以踩
through the code and view all the values
通过代码并查看所有值
for these variables inside the debug
对于调试中的这些变量
window here you can see all the
在这里的窗口，您可以看到所有
JavaScript that's being run inside the
正在内部运行的JavaScript
scripts panel of the debug window and
调试窗口的脚本面板和
here I'm working with the jQuery that
在这里，我正在使用的jQuery
comes with the spring application let's
附带了spring应用程序
resume our application and see what else
继续我们的申请，看看还有什么
we can do
我们可以做的
now on my back-end application I've set
现在在我设置的后端应用程序上
another breakpoint in this method here
这种方法的另一个断点
and so as soon as it hits the first line
所以一到达第一行
of this build feed entries method then
然后生成此构建提要条目方法
the debugger will pause at that line if
如果出现以下情况，调试器将在该行暂停
we go back to our application and select
我们回到我们的应用程序并选择
subscribe to atom feed then we'll stop
订阅原子供稿，然后我们将停止
at this location we can inspect all of
在这个位置，我们可以检查所有
the variables on our stack and again
我们堆栈上的变量
step through our code so let's resume
逐步执行我们的代码，让我们继续
this now and see we like to change the
现在，看看我们喜欢改变
implementation of this method so here
这种方法的实现，所以这里
inside each feed entry I'll just change
在每个供稿条目中，我都会更改
this string what I can do is save the
这个字符串我能做的就是保存
application reload this from the browser
应用程序从浏览器重新加载
resume this and because we've been able
继续执行此操作，因为我们已经能够
to update on frame deactivation and will
更新停用的框架，并将
find that our new implementation is now
发现我们的新实现现在
live on the server good
住在服务器上不错